

Profile

I have been dealing with various software as an amateur for about 10 years. In my early years I was involved with **CMS** systems (**Opencart**, **WordPress** etc). I have been working as a Frontend Developer with **JavaScript**, **ReactJS** (Redux), **NodeJS**, **HTML**, **CSS** and **MongoDB** for about 3 years.

J

Employment History

Front-End Developer at Freelance, Istanbul

2018 - 2022

- I have been working in the e-commerce industry for 4 years
- I know the problems or the sector and produce solutions to these problems.
- Mastered e-commerce terminology by working in the field
- Systems I used throughout the process: **Wordpress**, **Opencart** and basic **javascript**, **html** and **css**

Front-End Developer (Intern) at ETurnsoft, Turkey

2022 - 2022

- Working on User Management System with admin panel.
- Using JavaScript, HTML, CSS, ReactJs, NodeJs, Bootstrap, and MongoDB

Front-End Developer at Codelisa Teknoloji, Istanbul / Turkey

2022 - Present

- Developing Mobile and Web projects as Full-Stack.
- Technologies I use: Javascript, HTML, CSS, Typescript, ReactJs, NextJS, NodeJs, TailwindCss, Bootstrap (v5.x), StyledComponent
- Skills I Gained: Micro Front End Architecture, planned working principle,
 Team management and working with a team.



Education

Depertman of Economics at Karadeniz Teknical University, Trabzon 2010 - 2014

Full-Stack Web Development Bootcamp (with Agile Tegnology), SoftInnovas Bootcamp, Istanbul

2021 - 2022



Courses

Full-Stack Javascript Development at SoftInnovas, Istanbul 2021 - 2022

Details

Istanbul, Turkey +905301142548 halit.uzan@gmail.com

Links

Github : @halituzan Linkedin : @halituzan Twitter : @uzandev

Portfolio: halituzan.github.io

Skills

Javascript Typescript HTML CSS ReactJs NextJs NodeJs Micro Front End MongoDB **Bootstrap** Tailwindcss Git **Opencart** Wordpress Adobe Illustrator Adobe Photoshop

Languages

English (A2)

Hobbies

Camping, Fishing, Traveling, Flowers and Plants